Tear apart these memories of days
long past with your own hands
Please silence this sorrow
that still breathes inside me
Now, pierce the heart
that aches for love!
FULLMETAL ALCHEMIST 2
THE DEVIL OF THE RED ELIXIR
I gaze at the sky where tomorrow should arrive,
My heart, lost and wandering, can’t decide its stride
A bird beside me took flight,
I wonder if it found somewhere the light
Hey, won’t you let me ride
on your back as well?
And then,
At the highest place
Leave me behind, and let me be free,
From any kindness
Tear apart these memories of days
long past with your own hands
Please silence this sorrow
that still breathes inside me
Now, pierce the heart
that aches for love!